== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)I had a bad dream that
my best friend became a tyrant
(Sheldon:)and forced me to stay
up all night to work.
(Leonard:)Oh, I had a good dream that
when I carried you to bed,
(Leonard:)I let your head hit
the wall and I laughed.
(Penny:)Good morning.
(Leonard:)What is this?
(Amy:)Well, we didn't see you
last night,
(Amy:)we're not gonna see you today,
(Amy:)so we thought we could have
breakfast together.
(Leonard:)Oh, that is so nice.
Ow, it does hurt!
(Leonard:)So, what are you guys
gonna do today?
(Amy:)Well, Sheldon was supposed to go
(Amy:)to this party with me
this afternoon,
(Amy:)but I don't think
that's happening.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that was never happening.
(Penny:)Oh, I'll go.
(Penny:)I like a party.
(Amy:)Well, to be honest, it's not
like a "party" party,
(Amy:)it's more like a gathering
(Amy:)where scientists of different
disciplines get together
(Amy:)to share their work
and keep current
(Amy:)on what's going on
in other fields.
(Amy:)I don't know why
I called it a party, sorry.
(Penny:)It's okay, I'll still go.
(Leonard:)You don't think you'll be bored?
(Penny:)Oh, I'll have some wine
and listen to people go on
(Penny:)about crap I don't understand.
(Penny:)I mean, how is it any different